Guide to the Menu collection, 1851-[ca.1990].
Menu collection,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Menu collection, 1851-[ca.1990]
6452
Cornell University Library.
35.3 cubic ft.
Menus.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
A collection of over 10,000 menus, providing evidence of the manners, mores, and food habits of earlier times.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The core of the collection was assembled by Oscar Tschirky (1866-1943), known throughout the world as Oscar of the Waldorf. As maitre d'hotel of the Waldorf Astoria Hotel in New York City, from 1893 to 1943, he began a lifelong hobby of collecting menus, some of which were for functions he himself arranged, but most of which were of historical, gastronomic, or artistic importance. Upon his death, his menu collection, papers, and personal memorabilia were donated to Cornell University. The Hotel School Library has continued to add to the collection.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
A collection of over 10,000 menus, providing evidence of the manners, mores, and food habits of earlier times.
Many menus include prints or half-tones of historic people and places. They may also include featured speakers, detail organizational leadership, and provide biographical sketches of the famous and infamous, including Theodore Roosevelt, Wilbur and Orville Wright, and Oscar Hammerstein. They may dramatize historical events, such as a "luncheon to the California Promotion Committee on the occasion of the resumption of the hotel business in the burned district after the earthquake and fire on 18 April 1906"; the opening of the first tunnels of the Hudson and Manhattan Railroad Company under the Hudson River; and a dinner in honor of Louis Kossuth, the Hungarian patriot. Prohibition era menus indicated the availability of spirits to their clientele by tucking a small insert into the spine cord of the menu.
Also menus collected by Charles N. Pinco.
Also, menus collected by Ruth Wood Green from hotels and nightclubs in the 1940s.
SAMPLE LOCATIONS
Astor House, NYC
Delmonico's, NYC
Waldorf-Astoria, NYC
Arena, NYC
San Francisco, CA
Sherry's, NYC
Carlton Hotel, London, England
Bellevue-Stratford, Philadelphia
Eastman Hotel, Hot Springs, AR
Algonquin Club, Boston
Municipal Ferry Terminal, SI+
Bozanta Tavern
Grunewald Hotel, New Orleans
Bancroft Hotel, Worcester, MA
Biltmore Hotel, NYC
Hamilton Hotel, Washington, DC
Les Halles Centrale, Paris, France
Raleigh Hotel, Washington, DC
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University Library.
Subjects:
Menus--United States--History--19th century.; Menus--United States--History--20th century.; Menus--England--History--19th century.; Menus--England--History--20th century.; Menus--France--History--19th century.; Menus--France--History--20th century.; Gastronomy.; Dinners and dining.; Restaurants.
Form and Genre Terms:
Menus.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIAL
Database at The Nestlé Library Restaurant Menus Database
See also the volume titled The Charles N. Pinco collection of international restaurant menus: gathered between 1909 and 1958 from the major portion of the civilized world, call # TX728.P56 +.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Menus Collected by Oscar Tschirky
Series II. Menus Collected by Charles N. Pinco
Series III. Assorted US Menus
Series IV. Assorted Canadian Menus
Series V. Assorted International Menus
Series VI. Assorted Unknown Menus
CONTAINER LIST
- Menus Collected by Oscar Tschirky
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 000-896, Date Unknown (Box 1)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 897-901, Date Unknown (Box 2)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 902-904, Date Unknown (Box 3)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 905, Date Unknown (Box 4)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 906, Date Unknown (Box 5)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 907, Date Unknown (Box 6)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 908, Date Unknown (Box 7)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 909001-909125, Date Unknown (Box 8)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 909126-910089, Date Unknown (Box 9)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 910090-End, Date Unknown (Box 10)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 911, Date Unknown (Box 11)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 912, Date Unknown (Box 12)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 913, Date Unknown (Box 13)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 914, 915, Date Unknown (Box 14)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 916, Date Unknown (Box 15)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 917, 918, Date Unknown (Box 16)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 919, Date Unknown (Box 17)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 920, Date Unknown (Box 18)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 921, Date Unknown (Box 19)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 922-923, Date Unknown (Box 20)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 924-925, Date Unknown (Box 21)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 926, Date Unknown (Box 22)
  - Oscar of the Waldorf: 927-943, Date Unknown (Box 23)
- Menus Collected by Charles N. Pinco
  - Pinco #1, Date Unknown (Box 24)
  - Pinco #2, Date Unknown (Box 25)
  - Pinco, Date Unknown (Box 26)
  - Pinco, Date Unknown (Box 27)
  - West and Southwest 1-38, Date Unknown (Box 43A)
  - West and Southwest 39-69, Date Unknown (Box 43B)
  - East West Railroads, 1-38, Date Unknown (Box 44A)
  - East West Railroads, 39-83, Date Unknown (Box 44B)
  - New York Hotels and Clubs, World's Fair, 1-37, Date Unknown (Box 45A)
  - New York Hotels and Clubs, World's Fair, 38-81, Date Unknown (Box 45B)
  - Domestic and International 1-40, Date Unknown (Box 46A)
  - Domestic and International, 41-82, Date Unknown (Box 46B)
  - Europe, 1-50, Date Unknown (Box 47A)
  - Europe, 51-101, Date Unknown (Box 47B)
  - United States and Canada, 1-44, Date Unknown (Box 48A)
  - United States and Canada, 45-79, Date Unknown (Box 48B)
  - U.S., 1-43, Date Unknown (Box 49A)
  - U.S., 44-79, Date Unknown (Box 49B)
  - New York City, 1-36, Date Unknown (Box 50A)
  - New York City, 37-77, Date Unknown (Box 50B)
  - Steamship lines, American coast, Airways, 1-21, Date Unknown (Box 51)
  - Steamship Lines, Transatlantic, 1-20, Date Unknown (Box 52A)
  - Steamship Lines, Transatlantic, 21-39, Date Unknown (Box 52B)
  - Japan, 1-30, Date Unknown (Box 53)
  - New England, Connecticut, Delaware, Maine, Massachusetts, New Hampshire, Vermont, 1-14, Date Unknown (Box 54)
  - Hotel Ezra Cornell, Willard Straight Hall, Swedish American Line, Marth Van Rensselaer Hall, The Waldorf-Astoria Sert Ballroom, The New York Hilton Hotel, US Senate, Hotel Statler, Hotel Statler Buffalo, Date Unknown (Box 55)
- Assorted US Menus
  - The 21 Club Luncheon, Expression (Box 62, Folder 1)
    New York, NY
  - The 21 Club Luncheon, 1990-01-11 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - 707 Jet Clipper Menu, Pan American, Undated (Box 56, Folder 28)
    Miami, FL
  - 1789, 1973-10-13 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - A. Fuerst, Caterer, 1913-06-29 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - A&J Blue Claw Restaurant, 1986-08-07 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Cape May, NJ
  - Accomac Inn, Undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
    Contains descriptive pamphlet.
    Wrightsville, PA
  - L'Aiglon, 1972-12-06 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Alice's, Undated (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Lenox, MA
  - Alpsteg's, 1979-06-02 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Wayne, NJ
  - Angus Barn, 1982-11-16 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Raleigh-Durnham, NC
  - Andover Inn, Undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
    Andover, MA
  - Andover Inn, Partial Menu, Undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Andover Inn, Sunday Menu, Undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Andrea's, 1986-07-04 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    Edgarton, MA
  - Antoine's, Undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
    New Orleans, LA
  - Antoine's, Undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Antoine's, 1940 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Antoine's, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Antoine's, Postcard, Undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Antoine's, "Souvenir Du Restaurant Antoine", Undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
    The pamphlet contains a very long list of distinguished guests who dined at Antoine's.
  - Antony's Pier 4, 1976-03-25 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Boston, MA
  - The American Traveler Menu, American Airlines, Undated (Box 59, Folder 1)
    United States
  - Apple Orchard Restaurant, 1984-07-19 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - The Apple Pie Bakery Café, Undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
    Hyde Park, NY
  - The Arch, 1973-06-05 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Short Hills, NJ
  - The Arsenal at Old New Castle, 2001-12-09 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    New Castle, DE
  - The Arsenal at Old New Castle, 1972-08-17 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Delaware, NJ
  - L'Auberge Chez Francois, 2000-07-14 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    Great Falls, VA
  - Autre Chose, Undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
    Cambridge, MA
  - L'Auberge du Couchon Rouge, 1981-11-07 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    Contains postcard with record of meal
    Ithaca, NY
  - L'Auberge du Couchon Rouge, Undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - L'Auberge du Couchon Rouge, Undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
    Contains postcard with menu written on it.
  - Aurora Inn, Undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
    Aurora, NY
  - Autre Chose, Undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Backstage at Hisae's, 1984-02-22 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Backstage at Hisae's, Undated (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Backstreet, Undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Bahrs, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Highlands, NJ
  - Bahrs, 1986-08-08 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Bahrs, 1973-03-11 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Bali Hai, Undated (Box 57, Folder 1)
    San Diego, CA
  - Ballatines Restaurant, Undated (Box 57, Folder 1)
    Chicago, IL
  - Banfi's, Undated (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Bangkik Cuisine, Undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Barbetta, 1990-02-21 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Barnside Tavern, Undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
    Hannover, MA
  - Barralhina, Undated (Box 62, Folder 3)
    San Juan, Puerto Rico
  - Bavarian Chalet, 1978-09-1-1978-10-29 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    Includes Oktoberfest invitation, as well as a note on ongoing automation in the restaurant and upcoming events/changes.
    Guilderland, NY
  - Le Beaujolais, 1989-02-22 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Beaujolais Café, Dinner Menu, Undated (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Beansprout, Undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
    Medford, MA
  - Beaux Arts Ball Carte des Vins, Hotel Astor, 1936-12-04 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - The Beeches Restaurant and Paul Revere Lodge, Undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
    Rome, NY
  - Bel Canto, Undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
    Lexington, MA
  - Le Bellecour, Undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Le Bellecour, Dessert Menu, Undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Benihana Palace, 1971-10-06 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Berta's, 1970-08-07 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Haskell, NJ
  - Beverley Hills Hotel, 1949-02-12 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    Beverley Hills, CA
  - Bill's Gay Nineties, 1971-09-02 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Le Bistro, 1983-05-22 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Elmwood Park, NJ
  - Bistro Francais, 1982-08-22 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Georgetown, MD
  - The Black Dog Tavern, 1986-06-29 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Brasserie 812, 2006-01-01-2006-12-31 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Brasserie 812, 2006-01-01-2006-12-31 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Brennan's, Undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Bonnie Castle Manor, 1988-08-20 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Alexandria Bay, NY
  - Boston Bicentennial Luncheon Honoring Her Majesty Queen Elizabeth II and Hist Royal Highness the Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh, 1976-07-11 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    A bicentennial celebration of the Revolutionary War hosted by the mayor of Boston, Kevin H. White, at the Boston City Hall. The document includes the program of the event, the menu, and a guestlist. Finally, at the end of the document, there is a note that reads, "On July 11, in the year of America's Bicentennial, 1976, Her Majesty, Queen Elizabeth II and His Royal Highness The Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh, visited these Freedom Trail sites in Boston. Two hundred years after voices of liberty echoed through this historic city, we celebrate the strong friendship now shared by Boston and Great Britain."
  - Boston Globe "A Guide to Brunch," July 13, 1978, 1978-07-13 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Boston Globe, "Dining Out," October 18, 1979, 1979-10-18 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Boston Globe, "Dining Out," October 13, 1983, 1983-10-13 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Boston Globe "How to Satisfy Food Cravings," May 31, 1984, 1984-05-04 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Boston Globe, "Outdoor Cafes for all Reasons," July 26, 1984, 1984-07-26 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Boston Globe, "Tasty Takes," February 5, 1984, 1984-02-05 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Boston Globe Magazine, "What's Upstairs at the Pudding?", January 8, 1984, 1984-01-08 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Broker's, 1979-08-08 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Buongiorno Kosher Daily Breakfast, 1997-03-16-1997-03-23 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Buongiorno Lunch Menu, 1997-03-18 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Buongiorno Welcome Gala Dinner Menu, Undated (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Brussels Restaurant, Undated (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Burns Country Inn, 1974-04-24 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - The Cabin, Undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Burnside, LA
  - Café Centro, 1997-05-09 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Café Escadrille, Undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Burlington, MA
  - Café Iguana, 1990-03-23 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Café Louis XIV, Lunch Menu, 1948-07-02 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Café Louis XIV, Dinner Menu, 1948-07-02 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Camden Harbor Inn, 1984-08-18 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Camden, ME
  - Camden Harbor Inn, Sunday Brunch Menu, 1984-08-19 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Candlelight Room, 1952-06-27 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    A restaurant at the Hilton Arrowhead Springs Hotel and Spa, San Bernardino, CA.
    San Bernardino, CA
  - Cape Half House, Undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Cape Cod, MA
  - Cape Half House, Dessert Menu, Undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Carolina, 1989-10-21 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - The Carriage House, 2001 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    Milburn, NJ
  - Castagnola's, 1981-08-29 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    San Francisco, CA
  - Castiello's, Undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Castiello's, Undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the State of New York 161st Annual Banquet, 1929-11-21 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Chardas, Undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Brookline, MA
  - The Charleston Garden, 1974-04-05 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Cherry Croft Inn, 1972-07-15 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    Fredon Township, NJ
  - Le Cheval Blanc, 1972-03-17 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Chez La Mere Madeleine, 1977-02-09 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Newton Centre, MA
  - Chez Sophia's, 1987-07-16 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Hadley, NY
  - Chi-Chi's, Undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Several locations in Massachusetts listed on menu.
    Massachusetts
  - El Cholo, Undated (Box 63, Folder 3)
    Los Angeles, CA
  - Churbes, 1948-06-01 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Citro's, Undated (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Cloverleaf Tavern, 1988-12-22 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    Caldwell, NJ
  - Club Libretti, 1973-01-25 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    West Orange, NJ
  - Coffee Coffee, Undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Arlington, MA
  - The Colony Restaurant, 1971-03-24 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - The Colony Restaurant, Dejeuner, 1948-05-28 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - The Colony Restaurant, Diner, 1948-05-28 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Commander's Celebration, 1995-11-11 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Commander's Palace, Undated (Box 57, Folder 2)
    Pamphlet with two recipes and information about the restaurant.
  - Commander's Palace, Undated (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Commander's Palace, Undated (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Consuelo's, Undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Several locations in California listed on menu.
    California
  - Cookin with Jazz, 1995-11-11 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - The Copa Room, 1953-03-27 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - The Country Gourmet, Undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Mountain View, CA
  - The Court of Two Sisters, Undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - The Crazy Crab, Undated (Box 61, Folder 3)
    Sea Pine Circle, SC
  - Curtist House, Undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Woodbury, CT
  - David William Hotel, 1979-01-16 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    Coral Gables, FL
  - DB Kaplan's Delicatessen, Undated (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Db Kaplan's Delicatessen, Fronzen Fantasies: A Three Act Dessert Featuring the Most Expensive Ice Cream in the World, Undated (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - The Decatur Club, 1955-11-26 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    Decatur, IL
  - Delegates Dining Room, 1977-01-21 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Le Delice, 1982-06-02 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    Whippany, NJ
  - Dinner For 10 Persons, $3 Per Person., 1940-10-30 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    Written by a Mr. George Skouras.
  - Dinner in honor of the Pennant Winners of the New York National League Base Ball Club, 1911-10-28 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Dinner to Nicholas Murray Butler, 1932-02-11 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    The full title of the menus is as follows: Dinner to Nicholas Murray Butler in Celebration of the 30th Anniversary of his Presidency, the 50th anniversary of his Graduation, and the 70th Anniversary of his Birth.
  - Dinner to Pioneers of American Industries, 1928-10-24 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Distinguished Chef Series, Jacques Noe, 1975-04-06 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    Held by Cornell University in the Statler Hotel.
  - Distinguished Chef Series: "A Steamboat Cruise", Robert Elick, 1975-10-05 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Dorie's Ice Cream, Undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Dorothea Renaud Rieger Restaurant-Bar, Undated (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Dorothea Renaud Rieger Restaurant-Bar, Undated (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - The Dover Grille, Undated (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - The Dover Sea Grille, Undated (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - The Dubliner: An Irish Pub, Undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
    Washington, DC
  - The Dugout, 1973-04-05 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    Amityville, NY
  - Durgin-Park, Undated (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Durgin-Park, Undated (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Ed Zaberer's, 1972-07-29 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    Wildwood, NJ
  - Edmonds, Undated (Box 57, Folder 4)
    St. Louis, MI
  - Eighteenth Annual Banquet of the Ohio Society of New York Given for the Honorable William Howard Taft, Secretary of War, at the Waldorf Astoria, 1904-03-05 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Emersons, 1976-08-14 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    Wildwood Crest, NJ
  - The Emersons, 1975-05-23 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    Sunday, MA
  - Empire Luncheon Menu, Undated (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Empire Room, Menu from Hawaiian Islands, 1959-09-21 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Empire Supper Menu, Undated (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Essex Fells Country Club, 1974-04-14 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    Essex Falls, NJ
  - Essex Fells Country Club Trustees Dinner, 1990-11-17 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Essex Fells Country Club Trustees Dinner, 1993-12-31 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - L'etoile, 1986-07-01 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - The Explorer's Club Sheraton, 1982-04-27 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    West Palm Beach, FL
  - Famous Town Tavern Steak House, Undated (Box 63, Folder 6)
    Little Falls, NJ
  - Farrell's Ice Cream Parlour and Restaurant, Undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Farrell's Ice Cream Parlour and Restaurant, Undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Fifi's Café, Undated (Box 57, Folder 5)
    Pacific Grove, CA
  - The Fifty Fourth, 1984-08 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Figtree's Café, Undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
    Venice, California
  - Fine Arts Restaurant, Undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - The Fish Hopper, Undated (Box 57, Folder 5)
    Monterey, CA
  - The Flagstaff House, Undated (Box 56, Folder 6)
    Boulder, CO
  - La Fonda del Sol, Undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Fonda La Paloma, 1970-08-13 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - The Fort, Undated (Box 56, Folder 6)
    West Hempden, CO
  - The French Connection, 1979-01-15 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Friendly, Directory of Locations, Undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
    Directory of all US Friendly Locations. Location listed as town of headquarters.
    Wilbraham, MA
  - The Friendship Dinner: Given in Honor of the Distinguished Soliders who Have Directed War, of Statesman Who Have Negotioated or Advanced Peace, and of Pioneering Aviators Whose Flights Have Extended Good Will, 1931-10-21 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Fox and Hounds, 1947-12-11 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    Santa Monica, CA
  - Gage and Tollner, 1974-05-29 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Gallagher Restaurant and Bakery, 1988-12-11 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Gallagher's, 1981-06-20 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Gallagher's, 1981-03-28 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - The Garden Room, Undated (Box 59, Folder 6)
    Las Vegas, NV
  - The Galley, 1973-08-23 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    ME
  - The Garden Room, Dinner, 1953-03-27 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Gill's Grill, Undated (Box 60, Folder 7)
    Includes August 1st Dinner Specials, year unspecified.
    Westboro, MA
  - George Washington Manor, 1989-06-11 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Trenton, NJ
  - The Golden Door, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - The Golden Ox, 1969-09-21 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    Kansas City, KS
  - The Good Steer, 1972-05-22 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Goodman's Deli and Restaurant, Undated (Box 60, Folder 7)
    Peabody, MA
  - Gourmet Chalet, 2001-12-08 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Northampton, PA
  - Grand Café, 1982-04-14 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    Morristown, NJ
  - Grand Tier Restaurant, 1994-02-22 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Grand Tier Restaurant, 1992-09-22 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - La Grande Salade Saloon, 1983-12-17 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    Delaware
  - Granson's, Undated (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - The Green Tulip, Undated (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - The Greenhouse, 1981-10-10 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    Philadelphia, PA
  - Grendel's, Undated (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - La Grenouille, Undated (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Gumbo Shop, Undated (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - La Hacienda, Undated (Box 59, Folder 7)
    Albuquerque, NM
  - Haim's Deli, Undated (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Hal's Guide to Great Sandwiches and other Gustatory Delights, Undated (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - The Harbo, 1975-06-10 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    Parsippany, NJ
  - Hawthorne by the Sea, Dessert Menu, Undated (Box 60, Folder 8)
    Lists several locations in Massachusetts
  - Hearns Liquor, ` (Box 59, Folder 7)
    This document is really several stapled together. There are multiple wine lists, and two letters to customers. The first, from November 14th, 1940, tells us that Hearns has been able to gather together a great quantity of French wine, which is now impossible due to the war. Apparently, "this is probably the most outstanding achievement in the history of 'America's Largest Liquor Store.'" The next letter, from 1942, describes its liquor as "safe from the ruthless hands of the invaders."
  - Hearns Liquor Christmas Sale Advertisement, 1939-12-18 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - The Heritage Inn, 1983-10-23 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    Stanhope, NJ
  - Highlawn Pavilion, 1989-07-11 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Highlawn Pavilion, Undated (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Highlawn Pavilion, 1990-09-28 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Highlawn Pavilion, 1987-12-24 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Highlawn Pavilion, 1992-04-14 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Hilton Café International, 1964-04-22-1964-10-18 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    This menue comes from the 1964-65 World's Fair.
  - Hilltop Steakhouse, A panorama Tour of, Undated (Box 60, Folder 8)
    A pamphlet meant to give its reader a tour of the restaurant. Special attention is paid to the dining rooms, facilities, and ample parking.
    Saugus, MA
  - Historic Smithville Inn, 1983-09-04 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    Smithville, NJ
  - The Hofbrauhaus Restaurant, Undated (Box 59, Folder 7)
    Hallandale, FL
  - Homestead, 1989-11-22 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    Orange, MA
  - Hotel Algonquin, 1974-04-04 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Astor, Columbia Room Supper, Undated (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Astor, Dinner, 1937-03-28 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Astor, Dinner, 1937-03-19 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Astor, Dinner, 1938-07-25 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Astor, Drink Menu, Undated (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Astor, Employees' Party, 1940-07-07 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Astor, Menu, 1922-10-17 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Astor, Roof Dinner, 1939-07-04 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Astor, Roof Dinner, 1939-05-24 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Astor, Roof Dinner, 1940-09-18 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Astor, Thanksgiving dinner, 1920-11-25 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Hershey, 1995-09-22 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    Hershey, PA
  - Hotel Imperial Drink List, Undated (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Orlando, Undated (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Hotel Orlando, Undated (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Hotel Plaza Athenee, Undated (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel St. Regis, 1906-05-14 (Box 56, Folder 8)